districtm.ca 2017-01-31

# Data & Privacy Policy – District M

### District M Data & Privacy Policy

District M takes the privacy and protection of personal information very seriously. By using the District M’s services, we may collect information about you and use and disclose such information, as described in this Policy.

This Policy describes the collection and use of Personal Information and Anonymous Information by District M when you use District M’s Services or see ads served by District M. _We do not collect Personal Information_ but we do collect and use Anonymous Information as described in this Data & Privacy Policy from the following activities:

  * Publishers’ and partners’ websites or publications where District M Services may reside
  * Users to whom District M serves advertising content (i.e. either an ad was purchased by District M or advertising space on a website visited by a user is represented by District M)

“Personal Information” refers to contact information (e.g., name, address, e-mail address, phone number …) and any other non-public information that can be used to directly identify a specific individual.

“Anonymous Information” refers to any information, not associated with your Personal Information, that can be used to infer an individual’s characteristics but not specifically identify an individual.

BY USING THE DISTRICT M SERVICES OR SUBMITTING PERSONAL INFORMATION THROUGH OUR DISTRICT M SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS DATA & PRIVACY POLICY AND YOU EXPRESSLY CONSENT TO THE PROCESSING OF YOUR INFORMATION ACCORDING TO THIS POLICY.

### Data Collection

We collect information to provide better services to our clients and users – by which we mean that we use data in a respectful and responsible way to provide added value to publishers, advertisers and users.

### What data District M Collects

In order to better understand user behavior, District M collects the following user information.

Device Information | Location Information | Connection Information  
---|---|---  
·     Device type 

·     Operating system

·     Browser type

| ·     Country, Region, City 

·     Latitude/Longitude coordinates

| ·     ISP 

·     IP address  
  
In addition to the above information, District M collects high-level information on the URLs visited users who have been served advertising content by District M.

### Data Usage

As previously mentioned, District M makes use of the information it collects to deliver value to its publishers and users. This value is ultimately delivered as targeted advertising that is relevant to users and will provide an acceptable return on investment to advertisers and publishers. Below are some of the ways District M uses your data:

  * Understanding traffic patterns and ad performance
  * Create look-alike models for better ad targeting
  * Create interest-based user profiles based on browsing history
  * Reporting to publishers and advertisers

### Data Sharing

District M may provide data it has collected to partners and service providers in order to provide, maintain, and enhance its service offering. For example, District M may enter into data sharing agreements with third parties in order to:

  * Counter malicious activity or invalid traffic
  * Share aggregated data derived from its platforms with the intention of measuring performance
  * Share user lists (anonymized user id’s only) and segment data with 3rd parties to improve ad performance, targeting and/or relevance

District M will never share information that would compromise its own Data & Privacy Policy as outlined in this document.

### Data Privacy and Protection

District M takes the privacy and protection of your information very seriously. We do not collect any personally identifiable information (PII). PII data includes any information that can identify you as an individual (e.g. name, address, e-mail address, and/or phone number). The information we collect about you is what is considered as “anonymous” data. Anonymous data can include general location information, device, platform information and browsing data.

### Data Retention

We normally will retain data for as long as it is necessary to fulfill a legitimate business purpose or as required by law. If you are a publisher, we will delete any data pertaining to your account upon termination of your account.

### Sensitive Information

District M does not collect or aggregate sensitive information, such as health information, to tailor ads on behalf of our advertiser clients. Furthermore, District M does not knowingly collect or maintain information from individuals who are under 13 years old.

### Opting out of District M targeted advertising

District M respects your privacy and supports your right to share your information as you see fit. If you do not wish to have District M use your information to deliver targeted ads and other customized content, we give you the option to opt-out at any time.

[Click here to opt out of receiving our targeted ads in your browser](https://cdn.districtm.ca/optout.html)

Our opt-out tool only prevents us from collecting site visit data pertaining to you on the browser on which it is installed, and will only function if your browser is set to accept third-party cookies. If you delete an opt-out cookie from a browser’s cookie files, we will collect site visit data from that browser until an opt-out cookie is reset on that browser.

### Changes to the District M Data & Privacy Policy

The District M Data & Privacy Policy is subject to change as the online advertising regulations change. We reserve the right to modify this Policy at any time, in which case we will post the changes to this page, this website, and other documents to keep you informed of what data we collect, how we collect it, how we use it, and how, if applicable, we share it with third parties.

If you are a publisher doing business with District M, we will notify you via email, with a link to this page, that changes have been made to the Data & Privacy Policy.

### Questions?

If you have any questions or suggestions to make regarding our Data & Privacy Policy, please contact us at [privacy@districtm.ca](mailto:privacy@districtm.ca) .
